let multiquestions = [
    {
        question: "What is 8 + 19",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 7",
        AnswerA: "28",
        AnswerB: "29",
        AnswerC: "30",
        AnswerD: "31",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 10",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "21",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "23",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 3",
        AnswerA: "39",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "41",
        AnswerD: "42",
        correctAnswer: "41",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 41 + 6",
        AnswerA: "45",
        AnswerB: "46",
        AnswerC: "47",
        AnswerD: "48",
        correctAnswer: "47",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 + 22",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 11 + 17",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "26",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "28",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "33",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "35",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 + 19",
        AnswerA: "65",
        AnswerB: "66",
        AnswerC: "67",
        AnswerD: "68",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 + 57",
        AnswerA: "80",
        AnswerB: "85",
        AnswerC: "90",
        AnswerD: "95",
        correctAnswer: "80",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 + 70",
        AnswerA: "81",
        AnswerB: "82",
        AnswerC: "83",
        AnswerD: "84",
        correctAnswer: "83",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 38 + 43",
        AnswerA: "78",
        AnswerB: "79",
        AnswerC: "80",
        AnswerD: "81",
        correctAnswer: "81",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 + 36",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "63",
        AnswerC: "64",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 + 22",
        AnswerA: "86",
        AnswerB: "87",
        AnswerC: "88",
        AnswerD: "89",
        correctAnswer: "87",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 + 28",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 + 48",
        AnswerA: "71",
        AnswerB: "72",
        AnswerC: "73",
        AnswerD: "74",
        correctAnswer: "74",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 83 + 41",
        AnswerA: "124",
        AnswerB: "125",
        AnswerC: "126",
        AnswerD: "127",
        correctAnswer: "124",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 87 + 36",
        AnswerA: "123",
        AnswerB: "124",
        AnswerC: "125",
        AnswerD: "126",
        correctAnswer: "123",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 112 + 34",
        AnswerA: "144",
        AnswerB: "145",
        AnswerC: "146",
        AnswerD: "147",
        correctAnswer: "146",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 106 + 28",
        AnswerA: "131",
        AnswerB: "132",
        AnswerC: "133",
        AnswerD: "134",
        correctAnswer: "134",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 100 + 50",
        AnswerA: "135",
        AnswerB: "140",
        AnswerC: "145",
        AnswerD: "150",
        correctAnswer: "150",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 72 + 47",
        AnswerA: "119",
        AnswerB: "120",
        AnswerC: "121",
        AnswerD: "122",
        correctAnswer: "119",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 + 39",
        AnswerA: "137",
        AnswerB: "138",
        AnswerC: "139",
        AnswerD: "141",
        correctAnswer: "137",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 86 + 27",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "113",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 28 - 7",
        AnswerA: "20",
        AnswerB: "21",
        AnswerC: "22",
        AnswerD: "23",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 39 - 22",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 - 22",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "23",
        AnswerC: "24",
        AnswerD: "25",
        correctAnswer: "22",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 - 24",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 - 15",
        AnswerA: "6",
        AnswerB: "7",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25 - 11",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "14",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 23 - 6",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "16",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "17",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 - 12",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "7",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 65 - 13",
        AnswerA: "52",
        AnswerB: "53",
        AnswerC: "54",
        AnswerD: "55",
        correctAnswer: "52",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 71 - 9",
        AnswerA: "62",
        AnswerB: "63",
        AnswerC: "64",
        AnswerD: "65",
        correctAnswer: "63",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 66 - 12",
        AnswerA: "53",
        AnswerB: "54",
        AnswerC: "55",
        AnswerD: "56",
        correctAnswer: "54",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 89 - 22",
        AnswerA: "64",
        AnswerB: "65",
        AnswerC: "66",
        AnswerD: "67",
        correctAnswer: "67",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 93 - 37",
        AnswerA: "56",
        AnswerB: "57",
        AnswerC: "58",
        AnswerD: "59",
        correctAnswer: "56",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 98 - 34",
        AnswerA: "61",
        AnswerB: "62",
        AnswerC: "63",
        AnswerD: "64",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 76 - 19",
        AnswerA: "55",
        AnswerB: "56",
        AnswerC: "57",
        AnswerD: "58",
        correctAnswer: "57",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 91 - 27",
        AnswerA: "63",
        AnswerB: "64",
        AnswerC: "65",
        AnswerD: "66",
        correctAnswer: "64",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 - 27",
        AnswerA: "114",
        AnswerB: "115",
        AnswerC: "116",
        AnswerD: "117",
        correctAnswer: "117",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 149 - 36",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "113",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 122 - 8",
        AnswerA: "113",
        AnswerB: "114",
        AnswerC: "115",
        AnswerD: "116",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 136 - 28",
        AnswerA: "105",
        AnswerB: "106",
        AnswerC: "107",
        AnswerD: "108",
        correctAnswer: "108",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 150 - 50",
        AnswerA: "100",
        AnswerB: "105",
        AnswerC: "110",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "100",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 127 - 13",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 138 - 29",
        AnswerA: "107",
        AnswerB: "108",
        AnswerC: "109",
        AnswerD: "111",
        correctAnswer: "109",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 131 - 17",
        AnswerA: "112",
        AnswerB: "113",
        AnswerC: "114",
        AnswerD: "115",
        correctAnswer: "114",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 13 x 3",
        AnswerA: "33",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "41",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 4 x 2",
        AnswerA: "4",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "8",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 4 x 6",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 7",
        AnswerA: "46",
        AnswerB: "47",
        AnswerC: "48",
        AnswerD: "49",
        correctAnswer: "49",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 6 x 6",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "37",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 5 x 5",
        AnswerA: "23",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "27",
        AnswerD: "30",
        correctAnswer: "25",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 4 x 4",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "18",
        correctAnswer: "16",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 4 x 8",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "32",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 10 x 5",
        AnswerA: "35",
        AnswerB: "40",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "50",
        correctAnswer: "50",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 3 x 15",
        AnswerA: "43",
        AnswerB: "44",
        AnswerC: "45",
        AnswerD: "46",
        correctAnswer: "45",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 7 x 3",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 8 x 3",
        AnswerA: "24",
        AnswerB: "25",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "27",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 9 x 2",
        AnswerA: "14",
        AnswerB: "16",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "20",
        correctAnswer: "18",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 18 x 2",
        AnswerA: "34",
        AnswerB: "36",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "36",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 15 x 2",
        AnswerA: "25",
        AnswerB: "30",
        AnswerC: "35",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "30",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 17 x 2",
        AnswerA: "30",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "34",
        AnswerD: "36",
        correctAnswer: "34",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 x 4",
        AnswerA: "195",
        AnswerB: "196",
        AnswerC: "197",
        AnswerD: "198",
        correctAnswer: "196",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 35 x 8",
        AnswerA: "275",
        AnswerB: "280",
        AnswerC: "285",
        AnswerD: "290",
        correctAnswer: "280",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 67 x 7",
        AnswerA: "466",
        AnswerB: "467",
        AnswerC: "468",
        AnswerD: "469",
        correctAnswer: "469",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 9",
        AnswerA: "231",
        AnswerB: "232",
        AnswerC: "233",
        AnswerD: "234",
        correctAnswer: "234",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 x 11",
        AnswerA: "261",
        AnswerB: "262",
        AnswerC: "263",
        AnswerD: "264",
        correctAnswer: "264",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 27 x 12",
        AnswerA: "322",
        AnswerB: "324",
        AnswerC: "326",
        AnswerD: "328",
        correctAnswer: "324",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 36 x 16",
        AnswerA: "572",
        AnswerB: "574",
        AnswerC: "576",
        AnswerD: "578",
        correctAnswer: "576",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 26 x 12",
        AnswerA: "308",
        AnswerB: "312",
        AnswerC: "314",
        AnswerD: "316",
        correctAnswer: "312",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 48 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "12",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 44 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "13",
        AnswerC: "15",
        AnswerD: "17",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 39 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "15",
        correctAnswer: "13",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 24 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 32 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 28 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "4",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "8",
        correctAnswer: "4",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 49 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "3",
        AnswerB: "5",
        AnswerC: "7",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "7",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 45 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "2",
        AnswerB: "3",
        AnswerC: "6",
        AnswerD: "9",
        correctAnswer: "3",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 150 ÷ 25",
        AnswerA: "5",
        AnswerB: "6",
        AnswerC: "8",
        AnswerD: "10",
        correctAnswer: "6",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 135 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "13",
        AnswerB: "15",
        AnswerC: "17",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "15",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 110 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "9",
        AnswerB: "10",
        AnswerC: "11",
        AnswerD: "12",
        correctAnswer: "10",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 121 ÷ 11",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "9",
        AnswerC: "12",
        AnswerD: "13",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 144 ÷ 12",
        AnswerA: "8",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "14",
        AnswerD: "16",
        correctAnswer: "12",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 143 ÷ 13",
        AnswerA: "11",
        AnswerB: "12",
        AnswerC: "13",
        AnswerD: "14",
        correctAnswer: "11",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 76 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "16",
        AnswerB: "17",
        AnswerC: "18",
        AnswerD: "19",
        correctAnswer: "19",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 78 ÷ 3",
        AnswerA: "22",
        AnswerB: "24",
        AnswerC: "26",
        AnswerD: "28",
        correctAnswer: "26",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 152 ÷ 4",
        AnswerA: "37",
        AnswerB: "38",
        AnswerC: "39",
        AnswerD: "40",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 168 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "24",
        AnswerD: "26",
        correctAnswer: "24",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 304 ÷ 8",
        AnswerA: "32",
        AnswerB: "34",
        AnswerC: "36",
        AnswerD: "38",
        correctAnswer: "38",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 282 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "37",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 315 ÷ 15",
        AnswerA: "21",
        AnswerB: "22",
        AnswerC: "23",
        AnswerD: "24",
        correctAnswer: "21",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 189 ÷ 7",
        AnswerA: "26",
        AnswerB: "27",
        AnswerC: "28",
        AnswerD: "29",
        correctAnswer: "27",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 279 ÷ 9",
        AnswerA: "31",
        AnswerB: "32",
        AnswerC: "33",
        AnswerD: "34",
        correctAnswer: "31",
    },
    {
        question: "What is 234 ÷ 6",
        AnswerA: "36",
        AnswerB: "37",
        AnswerC: "38",
        AnswerD: "39",
        correctAnswer: "39",
    },
]